export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 20,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is the result of `typeof typeof 1`?',
      answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'string',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What will `console.log(1 === true)` output?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is the result of `"hello" instanceof Object`?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'What does `console.log([10] === [10])` return?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(1 + "2" + "2")`?',
      answers: ['122', '5', '14', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: '122',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'What is the output of `console.log(3 + 2 + "7")`?',
      answers: ['12', '327', '57', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: '57',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(Math.max())`?',
      answers: ['0', 'undefined', 'Infinity', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: '-Infinity',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(1 < 2 < 3)`?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'true',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'What is the result of `"5" - 3`?',
      answers: ['2', '8', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'What will `console.log(1 - "1")` output?',
      answers: ['0', '1', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: '0',
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'What is the output of `console.log(typeof NaN)`?',
      answers: ['number', 'string', 'NaN', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'number',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'What does the following code return: `console.log(typeof (typeof 1))`?',
      answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'string',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log([] + {})`?',
      answers: ['[object Object]', '{}', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: '[object Object]',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'What will the output of `console.log(1 + 2 + "3")` be?',
      answers: ['33', '123', '6', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: '33',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(+"hello")`?',
      answers: ['NaN', 'SyntaxError', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'NaN',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'What will the following code output: `console.log(!!"false")`?',
      answers: ['false', 'true', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'true',
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: 'What is the result of `console.log([] + [])`?',
      answers: ['[]', '{}', '0', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: '',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'What will be the output of `console.log(0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3)`?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'What will be the output of the following code: `console.log(typeof typeof 1)`?',
      answers: ['number', 'string', 'object', 'undefined'],
      correctAnswer: 'string',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'What is the output of `console.log(1 === true)`?',
      answers: ['true', 'false', 'undefined', 'TypeError'],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
  ],
};
